[English subtitles are available]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 17]
Mother of Trees,
do you remember
what he said to me?
I said
life is long.
What if I can't afford you?
He said.
-Then I'll sell myself to you. -Then I'll sell myself to you.
-One tael. -One tael.
-Okay? -Okay?
One tael.
I wanted to cry when I heard it.
Too expensive?
How about
one copper coin?
He is such a calculating person.
He wanted to do it for one copper coin.
♫In the sea of clouds, I looked at the reflection of the moon in the water♫
Then,
I gave him one copper coin.
♫I kept waiting and arched my palms into a circle♫
One copper coin.
He promised me for a lifetime.
♫The reflection gradually reminded me of our first meeting♫
Lu Li is sold to Liu Shao.
Will you regret it?
Never.
♫I can no longer tell the difference between wind and rain♫
For a lifetime.
♫Even if I get the volley sword♫
If I miss you,
♫I can't forget you♫
I'll regret it for the rest of my life.
♫Our destiny has been sealed long ago♫
Then don't.
♫I have no other choice♫
♫Why have you been so far away from me every time♫
♫For billions of years♫
♫Can I use your hands to warm up the world again?♫
♫A few hasty nights♫
♫Too many intertwined oaths and lies♫
I didn't expect
♫Have shattered my dreams♫
a lifetime is so short.
♫Who would like to take a broken willow branch♫
Love is bitter.
♫And watch the moon alone in the blue sky♫
You don't have to be
so sad.
Let it go.
Mother of Trees.
Go away!
Go to your heartless master!
So what if you suppress love?
Back then,
Lu Li once swore to me
and promised me for a lifetime.
If you really have any trace of Lu Li,
you should ask yourself.
Is today's ending
worthy of the flowers blooming that day?
Water hyacinth.
Say something.
♫Even if I get the volley sword♫
♫I can't forget you♫
♫Our destiny has been sealed long ago♫
Mother of Trees.
Here's to you.
♫I have no other choice♫
♫Why have you been so far away from me every time♫
Here's to you.
♫For billions of years♫
Now I think about it.
♫Can I use your hands to warm up the world again?♫
I'm like your Demon Queen.
♫A few hasty nights♫
We're in the same boat.
We all met
♫Too many intertwined oaths and lies♫
a man like this.
In the end,
♫Have shattered my dreams♫
we are alone
♫Who would like to take a broken willow branch♫
with a miserable ending.
♫And watch the moon alone in the blue sky♫
Why is it wet?
Why is it raining?
Mother of Trees.
♫The remaining flowers in the mirror reflect the moon in the water♫
Are you crying?
I see.
I know why you are crying.
♫We can't live up to such a good time♫
What you love
hurt you the most.
♫Recalling the unforgettable glance at the beginning♫
What can I do? He will never come back.
♫I realized that it was a thousand years ago♫
♫Is this bad luck, or good luck?♫
♫He said that responsibility and love are difficult to balance♫
♫He had no choice but to leave me♫
♫The past has passed, so do not linger♫
You're drunk.
♫My love for you is still so strong♫
Let me send you back.
♫Too many intertwined oaths and lies♫
Lu Li.
♫Have shattered my dreams♫
♫Who would like to take a broken willow branch♫
I miss you so much.
I really miss you.
♫And watch the moon alone in the blue sky♫
No.
♫Life is like a grain of sand♫
You're not him.
♫It burns the fire in my heart♫
♫I want to burn myself to hear you say♫
You bastard.
♫You have never changed♫
But I miss him.
I feel terrible.
Let me send you home.
No.
Drunk Mother of Trees.
Even the Demon King hasn't seen her like this.
No wonder the Immortal Luo Ge has to give in.
Mr. Tai.
Come and help me.
My brother has trapped me.
I'm afraid something bad will happen.
We have the same heart.
Why are people different?
Are you Lu Li
only in my dream?
Love
is unpredictable.
It's just like a dream.
Why can't you understand it?
About what?
After you return to the Immortal Palace,
think about it carefully
and forget the past.
Forget?
I don't want to forget. Who wants to forget?
You forget it.
Put me down.
Why are you looking at me?
Immortal Luo Ge.
What do you want?
He Na.
He...
He wants me to erase my memory.
Liu Shao.
Help me.
Forget the past?
Go and do it yourself.
Don't touch me.
I don't want to forget.
I'm asking her
to go back to Immortal Palace with me
and cultivate.
I think she's doing well now.
She is passionate.
That's who she is.
Why bother to change it?
Exactly.
Are you looking for me?
Is there any news about the Lusitai Incident?
Yes.
Please tell me.
It was...
It was done by a heresy of the Demons,
half-demon Lu Sheng.
Fu.
I'm Fu of the Aquatic Demons.
Greetings, Immortal Luo Ge.
Half-demon Lu Sheng?
Yes.
Immortal Luo Ge
must be familiar with this name.
Half-demon Lu Sheng
is half-demon and half-human.
He is good at the formation
and loves collecting magic tools.
He's a loyal subordinate of the God of the Moonlight.
During the battle between the two gods,
half heart of the God of the Moonlight
was suppressed under the Four Seasons Monument.
Lu Sheng
is the one and only
who wants to topple the Four Seasons Monument most
in the world.
Did he
give the string to you?
Bone-Corroding Harp was broken that day,
and it infuriated the Immortal Palace.
They forced the Aquatic Demons to repair it within three days.
I had no choice
but went to Lu Sheng.
He gave me the string.
And I
gave the string
to the Demon King.
But this has nothing to do with him.
It's all my fault.
If you don't believe me,
you can check Lu Sheng's residence.
You have performed a Protection Spell here.
We can't escape.
Where is Lu Sheng now?
She knows.
Lu Sheng is Lu Li's master.
She knows him.
It's more comfortable to sleep at He Na's place.
Immortal Luo Ge.
Why are you here?
Aren't you waiting for He Na to find out the truth?
After you take me to find someone,
maybe the truth will come out.
Immortal, your face...
What happened?
A dog bit me.
What kind of dog
is so gentle and left such few marks?
You'd better learn the Dog-Beating Stick from the human.
Maybe
it can protect your fair face.
Liu Shao.
I wonder if your head
can take my Dog-Beating Stick?
You are not him.
You bastard.
Immortal.
Yesterday, I...
Shut up.
One more word,
I'll make you can't talk for three days.
The things were exposed.
Luo Ge will be here soon.
You can use this magic weapon
to make Luo Ge lose his power temporarily.
Take this chance to kill Liu Shao.
You can imprison Luo Ge here.
I have a way to persuade him
to split the Four Seasons Monument
and become
the real God of the Moonlight.
What are you writing?
Over the wastelands,
there is an oasis in the northwest.
The person living there
is an elder of our race.
Take this letter to him.
Luo Ge set a Protection Spell here.
I will work with all my people
to break the Protection Spell
and send you away.
You don't trust me?
Fu,
We've grown up together.
No one knows you better than me.
The incident of Luositai
must have something to do with you.
You trapped me last night
because you wanted to find Luo Ge
and admit that the spirit vein is yours
and take everything I did,
right?
You have to leave now.
Answer me.
You are arrogant
because you have been trapped in the water.
I don't blame you for doing this
because you feel unfair in your heart.
But Fu,
most of the dead are innocent.
Someone has to take the blame.
I'm the Demon King
and your brother.
This is what I should do.
So do you think
you are really doing this for me?
This is the only thing I can do for you.
But that's not what I want you to do.
Fu,
What did you put in the tea?
Debilitating Powder.
The most common drug in the demon world.
Brother.
Let me tell you
what I really want you
to do for me.
Brahma Lotus.
This is really a top-class magic weapon.
It is made with the Demon Palace's tens of thousands of years of history.
It is really amazing.
Brother,
did you sleep well?
What exactly do you want?
Do you want to be the Demon King?
If I really want to be the Demon King,
would you give it to me?
If you really want it,
I can give it to you.
Demon King in White.
His race is cursed.
They can't leave the water
and be restricted everywhere.
And they have to lower their heads to others.
Why do I want
such a title?
What exactly do you want?
I want my brother to come back.
I'll do anything for that.
Lu Li planted this for me.
It's very sweet.
Mr. Lu Sheng.
Do you remember Lu Li planted the pear tree for you?
But he's not the first person
to plant the pear tree for me.
I'm a half-demon.
Both humans and demons hate me.
A long time ago,
I was exiled to an extremely cold place.
I was infected with lung disease.
One day,
an amazing person came
and adopted me.
Because I have a cough,
he planted a pear tree for me.
Every year,
he picked the first pear for me.
Who said you can't practice magic?
You are not useless.
From now on,
I will teach you the formation.
After you master it,
you can use the formation
to teach those who bullied you a lesson.
The one who gave you pears
is the God of the Moonlight?
Yes.
So you want the God of the Moonlight to come back,
as well as the half of the heart?
But you know
what's inside that half of the heart.
If it reappears,
the three worlds will be in misery.
What does it have to do with me?
All I did in my life
is for the God of the Moonlight.
I don't understand.
Why did you set him up?
Why did you kill him?
Lu Li got killed because of you.
You made him lose his mind.
Now,
you're here to hurt him.
You are his destined enemy.
I won't let you go.
Luo Ge.
This magic weapon can trap Luo Ge.
Now it's time to kill Liu Shao.
No.
Someone tampered with the formation.
Lu Sheng.
This is not the Immortal Trapping Formation.
This is the Immortal Devouring Formation.
This formation
will kill everyone around
no matter if you are a human or an immortal.
We will all die under this formation.
Even you can't escape.
It's Fu.
Fu tampered with the Brahma Lotus.
Luo Ge has the strongest spiritual power.
So the first one to be devoured by the Immortal Devouring Formation
is him.
Oh no.
Luo Ge!
You can't die.
She activates the Sun Spirit to attract the Immortal Devouring Formation.
Why?
Why did she do that?
Why do I feel heartbroken?
I can't let Liu Shao die for me.
Moon Sword!
No!
Don't use your vitality.
A large amount of spiritual power will release
and you will die for sure.
If you die,
who else can I find
to be the God of the Moonlight in this world?
In this world,
only the God of the Moonlight and Li
would plant the pear tree and make pear soup for me.
But I sacrificed Li's life
and failed to save the God of the Moonlight.
It seems
I won't get to see your return.
But at least
I can still protect half of the God's heart.
Lu Sheng,
if you master the formations and spells I taught you,
I hope you can get rid of the restriction of your half-demon identity
and live your life
the way you wish to.
Unfortunately,
it's too late for me.
Don't waste your spiritual power.
It's useless.
I have only one obsession
in my life.
That is to bring the God back.
Because of it,
I adopted Lu Li.
Master, I'm back.
Master.
I'll make you Chuanbei herb-pear juice.
It's sweet.
I'm sure you'll like it.
In this way,
I can find the best doctor in the world
and buy the best and most expensive medicine for you.
Master,
you are ill.
Take care of yourself.
You can live your own life
and love the one you love.
You
don't seem to want me to be with her.
You can't be together.
You want to know your identity,
so I asked you to come to the  Mansion of Wu Yang Duke
to pull out the Moon Sword,
not to enjoy romance.
Master,
if I become the God of the Moonlight,
Liu Shao will die.
You want to sacrifice an innocent person.
Why don't you start with me?
Fine.
Give me back half of your heart.
Do you really want to die for her?
You value this half of the heart so much.
Liu Shao has filled it with....
Master,
remember to take your medicine on time.
Take care.
Lu Li.
It's my obsession that killed you.
I'm sorry.
Be careful of Fu.
[Half-demon Lu Sheng]
Why did you save me?
Don't think too much.
Immortals are merciful.
No matter who is in danger,
I will save them.
And you are one of the living.
I can't
let you die.
What is this?
The Tears of the Half-Demon Lu Sheng just shed.
[Half-demon Lu Sheng's Tomb]
What I want is
the ambitious you from 9000 years ago.
You were gentle
but full of ambition.
You can leave the water.
You can be free.
You have become like this
because of me.
Fu,
you are right.
I was too arrogant when I was young.
I just practiced the flute here.
What does it have to do with you?
Cut the crap.
Nothing good comes out of
Aquatic Demons coming to the Human world.
How dare you resist, you demon?
A man should have dignity and not kneel.
It seems that the Immortal Palace
regards dignity as garbage.
My brother
was the pride of the Aquatic Demons.
The people who had been bullied, including me,
saw the hope of the Aquatic Demons in you.
Back then...
it was my fault.
I was too impulsive
and got everyone into trouble.
Brother.
Fu.
You're finally back.
Demon King.
What do you want?
How dare you Aquatic Demons
insult the people from the Immortal Palace?
What do you think I want?
He insulted me.
I didn't hurt him.
Let go of Fu!
Don't hurt my brother!
I think you won't regret it until you see the result.
Do you want to know how your people died?
My Pearl of Fire
can absorb the water in the body.
Let me show you.
Brother.
Don't worry about me.
Kill them!
Kill them all!
You have guts.
I admire you.
Open his mouth.
Make him swallow it.
No!
What did you say?
Please don't.
You're begging me now.
But I remember
you were mocking us immortals.
You said we don't have dignity
and kneel.
Brother.
Don't.
Don't!
No.
Can you let Fu go?
Yes.
As long as you
swallow it,
I'll let him go.
No.
No!
Brother!
Demon King!
Brother.
He Na.
You're a rare genius
with amazing magic,
and you can leave the water,
but what's the use?
Look at your brother.
Can he leave this place?
Can the Aquatic Demons
leave this place?
How dare you
disrespect the world
and fight against us immortals?
Stay here
and be an inferior race.
Brother.
Brother!
They said we are an inferior race.
They said you are not qualified to be proud.
They said you're not qualified to challenge the Immortal Palace.
But do you really admit it?
The Pearl of Fire you swallowed
has hurt you for ten years.
Have you forgotten?
Even if you have forgotten,
I remember everything.
I remember his name is Xie Lingqi.
He was frustrated in the Immortal Palace
and he dared to come to the Aquatic Demons to mess around.
I caught him with Lu Sheng
and threatened him.
You are...
It's you.
It's been 900 years.
Practitioner Xie.
How are you?
It's useless.
Do you know who taught Lu Sheng
the formations?
It's the God of the Moonlight.
When you forced my brother,
have you ever thought about today?
Fine.
I was wrong.
Let me go.
Don't kill me.
You're a practitioner from the Immortal Palace.
How can you beg for mercy from an inferior person?
Listen to me.
I can't die.
I can't die yet.
I haven't got what I want yet.
Someone is waiting for me.
What you want.
Lord Wuxiang of the Immortal Palace
would be promoted to an Immortal probably.
Immortal Master Wanwu will be promoted too.
Can you get
what you want in your life?
How about this?
Let's work together.
Help me do what I want,
and I'll get what you want.
What do you think?
He agreed to cooperate with me.
Later,
Luo Ge set a trap for him.
I forced him to jump in.
I gave him demon energy.
This is for you. It's demon energy.
You know what to do.
I used the Water Hyacinth Spell
to get his demon aura into his bones
and make everyone of the Immortal Palace
think he was a spy of the demon world.
He couldn't defend himself
and was thrown into the Bone-melting Pool.
Brother,
I get avenge for you.
Stop thinking about the past
and be free again.
Fu,
from the day I became the Demon King,
I have no freedom.
I want to give it back to you.
I did these
cruel things,
not for the title of Demon King.
You are my brother.
You knelt for me
and swallowed the Pearl of Fire for me.
I would do anything.
I want to topple the Four Seasons Monument
and overthrow the world.
I want to give you freedom.
But if we can find the immortal energy of Immortal Ze Shui,
we can also save our people.
You don't have to sacrifice so many lives.
Enough.
Because you know
it's useless.
Your Majesty,
Immortal Luo Ge and Miss Liu are back.
They want to see you and General Fu.
Luo Ge?
He's not dead.
There is no actual evidence
that it has something to do with Fu.
Then please tell me
which one of you Aquatic Demons let the news slip?
Is that you?
He Na.
The Immortal is just taking Fu back to imprison him temporarily.
It will be fine.
I'm the Demon King.
If I say no,
it's no.
Unfortunately,
in this small Aquatic Demons,
not everyone listens to the Demon King.
I'll go.